(Man in seat behind:)it's neither.
(Man in seat behind:)They actually use
the AAR type "E" coupler.
(Man in seat behind:)If you listen carefully when
the locomotive disconnects,
(Man in seat behind:)you'll hear the characteristic
click, whoosh,
(Man in seat behind:)...thunk of the knuckle.
(Sheldon:)Get out of town.
(Howard:)I'm gonna
jump off this train.
(Leonard:)Hey, Cinnamon,
guess who just did it human style.
Oh, my God!
(Leonard:)It's a little late, but I'll take it.
(Penny:)No, Cinnamon ate the chocolates.
That's really bad for dogs.
(Leonard:)Oh, crap.
What are we gonna do?
(Penny:)We gotta get her to a vet right now.
(Leonard:)I don't have a vet.
I have a podiatrist,
(Leonard:)an optometrist, an allergist,
a dermatologist, a urologist.
(Leonard:)You'd think I'd have a vet.
OK. There's one not far from here.
(Penny:)-Come on. Let's go.
-OK.
(Leonard:)Koothrappali was right.
We should have let her watch.